amazingtechproducts.com 2013-07-26

# Privacy Policy | Amazingtechproducts.com - Amazing Tech in Action

**By accessing this site, you agree that you have read and understand the Amazing Tech Products Inc S-Corp privacy statement which describes how we use your personal information, and what options you have to update or request the deletion or correction of information submitted to us via www.AmazingTechProducts.com.com**

By accessing this site, you agree that you have read and understand the Amazing Tech Products Inc S-Corp (AmazingTechProducts.com, we, our, us, etc.) privacy statement (Statement) which describes how we use your personal information, and what options you have to update or request the deletion or correction of information submitted to us via [www.AmazingTechProducts.com.com](http://www.amazingtechproducts.com.com/ "www.AmazingTechProducts.com.com") (Site). If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this Statement, please do not use the Site.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT & WHY

Personal Information Submitted By You. We collect Personal Information you provide to us for purposes of (a) signing up for our newsletter; (b) submitting comments to us regarding vendors, products for this Site; (c) filling out and submitting one of our online surveys; (d) participating in one of our contests; and (e) your general use of the Site such as your participation in one of our online Forums.

The practices described in this Statement may also apply to Information you provide to us in writing or by telephone, such as when you contact our customer service staff. Personal Information may include items such as your name, address, telephone number, zip code, age, and income level. Unless you provide it to us voluntarily, AmazingTechProducts.com does not collect Personal Information about you in connection with your use of this Site.

Information Pertaining to Minors. AmazingTechProducts.com does not wish to collect Personal Information from minors (children under 13 years of age, or any other age defined under applicable law). If we become aware that a minor is attempting to or has submitted Personal Information via this Site, we will notify the user that we may not accept his or her Personal Information. We will then delete any such Personal Information from our records.

Automatic Transactional Information. Certain Non-personal Information may be collected automatically as part of your use of this Site, as well as from your transactions with us and our affiliates or nonaffiliated third parties. This Non-personal Information is used to improve the overall Site operations, functionality and appearance. Non-personal Information may include your IP address, web browser type, domain name and the time or date upon which you visited the Site.

Cookies, Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs). Cookies may be used by us in order to retain state-specific information and remember which menus should be displayed. Cookies are small data files that are stored on an Internet user's computer by a web server and may be used by some of the advertisers in the ads contained in our Site. Our Site may also include clear gifs within the third party advertising appearing on the Site. Clear gifs permit the tracking of user movement in the aggregate and are not tied to specific email addresses or other personal identifiers. AmazingTechProducts.com has no access to the aggregate information compiled by third party clear gif usage.

### HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

Personal Information is used by AmazingTechProducts.com for the purpose for which it was submitted. For example, if you submit your email address and other information required to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use that Personal Information to send you our newsletter. Please see below for your Choice/Opt Out options.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Site.

If a user elects to use our "Tell A Friend" referral service for informing a friend about our Site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the Site, both email addresses are not stored.

### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

Demographic and aggregate Information may be shared by us with third party advertisers. Aggregate Information contains no personal identifiers. We do not share, sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties for their promotional use.

AmazingTechProducts.com makes every reasonable effort to preserve user privacy. However we reserve the right to disclose Personal Information when required or permitted by law and we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with an appropriate law enforcement investigation, current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us.

### SALE OR TRANSFER OF INFORMATION

In the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, or transfer of part of the business, trade or assets of AmazingTechProducts.com, all Information collected about you via this Site may be sold, assigned, or transferred to the party acquiring all or substantially all of the equity or assets or business of AmazingTechProducts.com. Subject to your election to opt out as described below, by using this Site, you consent to the sale and transfer of your information as described in this paragraph.

### SECURITY

This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the Information under our control. All employees are aware of our policies. Safeguards are in place to keep sensitive data secure via the use of passwords.

### THIRD PARTIES; LINKS

Linking. This Statement applies only to [http://www.AmazingTechProducts.com](http://www.amazingtechproducts.com/ "http://www.AmazingTechProducts.com"). This Site may include links to the web sites of both our affiliated and non-affiliated entities (Other Sites), including access to content, products and services of such affiliated and non-affiliated entities. Other than as described below under "Co-Branding", whenever you choose to access Other Sites or non-AmazingTechProducts.com' content via this Site, a separate browser window will launch and you will leave this Site. We urge you to familiarize yourself with the individual privacy and other terms for each linked site prior to submitting your Personal Information.

Co-Branding. We also have co-branding relationships with other organizations. Although these areas of the Site may have the same (or a similar) look and feel as our Site and therefore may appear to be part of our Site, they have their own privacy policy available respectively. We utilize Topica for our mailing list function, they have their own privacy policy. We urge you to familiarize yourself with their policies prior to using these services.

### BULLETIN BOARD/CHAT ROOM

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

### AMAZINGTECHPRODUCTS.COM IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRODUCTS, PRICES, PRIVACY PRACTICES OR CONTENT OF OTHER SITES

Third Party Service Providers. AmazingTechProducts.com works with a third party that serves ads to this Site.

### OTHER TERMS

Your use of our Site is subject to and contingent upon your agreement with our Terms of Use, which are hereby incorporated by reference.

### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

Users will be notified of changes to this Statement by a notice posted on the Site within thirty business days prior to the changes taking effect. Any material change in how Personal Information is collected or used by AmazingTechProducts.com or the third parties referenced in this Statement will cause a notice to be posted. An email will also be sent to registered newsletter readers when a change is made, giving them the opportunity to opt-out.

### CONSENT

By using this Site, you consent to the use, storage and disclosure of your Information by us in the manner described in this Statement. We reserve the right to make changes to this Statement from time to time and will alert you to such changes via the Notification procedure described in the preceding paragraph.

### CHOICE/OPT-OUT

Our Site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request Information from you.   
In addition, to request that we remove you from our database or stop sending you future communications, by emailing us at [unsubscribe@amazingtechproducts.com](mailto:unsubscribe@amazingtechproducts.com?subject=unsubscribe).

### CORRECT/UPDATE

Users may submit requests to AmazingTechProducts.com for changing, deleting, and modifying Personal Information previously submitted, by sending an email to [contact@amazingtechproducts.com](mailto:contact@amazingtechproducts.com?subject=Request%20to%20change%2C%20delete%20or%20modify%20Personal%20Information).
